根据真实事件改编
纽约 山谷村舍 二零零一年
我无数次想过逃离这个地方
I left this place a thousand times in my mind,
可我从未离开过
but I never actually went anywhere.
最后一根稻草是什么
What was the final straw?
我一无所有
I had nothing.
不和的家庭
There's the unsupportive family.
不 我才不在乎她想要什么
No, I don't give a crap if that's what she wants.
她想住在老娘家里无所事事那可没门
She's not gonna sit in my goddamn house and do nothing!
一份绝望的工作
The dead-end job.
# 丛林儒先生他上又下 #
Jungle Ru went up and down.
# 开始一个大冒险 #
On a big adventure.
然后因为宿醉未消 绝望的工作也没了
Then getting fired from the dead-end job for being hungover.
那个...
Yeah...
工作不是这么糊弄的 我知道
This isn't working.I get it.
梅根 你只是不善于与他人相处
Megan, it's just, you don't really connect with people very well.
我很抱歉成为告诉你这事的人
I'm sorry to be the one to tell you this.
不 不 没关系
No, no, no, it's fine.
真的
Really.
到最后 离开不是因为有了目的地
In the end, you don't leave because you have somewhere to go.
离开是因为这里毫无留恋
You leave because there's nothing keeping you there.
征兵中心
离开这里 见识世界
变得可靠 诚实正直 有判断力
我只知道自从我最好的朋友去世
All I know is that after my best friend died,
这儿已没有让我留恋的东西了
there was nothing left for me here.
我已经彻底脱离了生活
I checked out of life completely.
我意识到 如果现在不离开
And I realized if I didn't leave now,
我永远都无法走出他离去的阴影
I wasn't gonna be far behind him.
西海岸长途客车
巴勒克街影业 利德尔娱乐 联合出品
由于安保措施增强
Due to heightened security measures,
请保持行李物品随身携带
please keep bags with you at all times.
所有无人看守的行李将会被没收
All unaccompanied luggage will be confiscated.
梅根 利维
- 你好 - 喂
- Hello? - Yeah.
在你梳妆台上的海军陆战队宣传册是怎么回事
Uh, what is this pamphlet for the Marines that I found in your dresser?
如果你继续翻 我放袜子的抽屉里还有点大麻
I think there's some pot left in the sock drawer if you keep digging.
别跟我耍聪明 这是我的房子
Yeah, don't be a wise ass, this is my house.
一走了之解决不了任何问题
And just so you know, running away isn't gonna solve anything,
- 因为你只会逃避... - 把电话挂掉
'cause that's all you've ever done... Hang up that phone!
快下车
Let's go!
动起来 快 快 快
Let's go, move, move, move.
动起来 再快点 快走 快 快
Let's go, faster, come on, move, move.
- 把衬衫掖进去 - 我的衬衫
- Tuck in that shirt! - My shirt?
把衬衫掖进去
Tuck your shirt in!
整理下你的头发
Fix your hair!
排好队 快点 动起来 快
Get in line, move! Let's go, move.
你们即将成为世界最强大军事力量的一员
You have taken the first step in becoming a member
这是你们的第一步
of the world's finest fighting force,
美利坚合众国海军陆战队
the United States Marine Corps.
成千上万的海军陆战队员就是从这里
Tens of thousands of Marines have begun outstanding service
开始为国效力
for our country starting right here.
你们要保持这优良的传统 明白了吗
You will continue that proud tradition.Do you understand?
是 长官
Aye-aye, sir!
用心点说
Say it like you mean it.
- 明白了吗 - 是 长官
- Do you understand? - Yes, sir!
集中训练营
帕里斯岛 南卡罗来纳州
起床 起床
Right now, right now.
我让你动 就赶紧动
When I tell you to move, you better move!
海军陆战队
Marine Corps!
你真是个耻辱
You're an embarrassment!
我说三 加速
I said three, step up.
从墙上滚下来
Get off my wall.
我能行
I can make it!
放开绳子 滚到队伍的最后面去
Get off my rope and get to the back of the line.
手臂伸直 利维
Get those arms straight, Leavey!
手臂伸直
Get those arms straight!
我让你伸直
I want straight arms!
在战场上你死定了 你听见了吗
You're gonna die out there,you hear me?
毕业分级的时候有你好看
Have fun at the graduation.
你这个废物
You're a failure.
从我眼前滚开
Get out of my face.
向前 看
Ready, front.
五零零四排
Platoon 5004,
解散
dismissed!
是 长官
Aye-aye, ma'am!
梅根
Megan?
嗨
Hello!
- 嗨 - 我们赶上了
- Hi. - Hi. We made it.
并没有 你们其实错过了 但...
Well, you didn't. You actually missed it, but...
你看起来像个小玩具兵
Ah! You look like a little toy soldier.
很好 谢谢
Great, thanks.
你们错过了整个仪式 但是没关系
You missed it, the whole ceremony, but that's okay.
- 真的吗 - 是啊 已经结束了
- Really? - Yeah, it's over.
吉姆 他非常想看到你毕业
Jim... He really wanted to see you graduate.
天哪 还以为我们纳税人交给军队的钱
Geez, you'd think with all the taxes we give to the military,
都只用在街头的宣传板上
they'd come up with some kind of street sign situation.
- 嘿 健将 - 嘿
- Hey, sport. - Hey.
亲爱的 我们错过了
Honey, we missed it.
- 错过了 - 嗯
- We missed it? - Mmm-hmm.
你能为我们再来一遍么
Can you do it again for us?
■
美国政府
"美国政府不会也不允许
"The United States will not and cannot run that risk
让美国人民承担这种风险
to the American people.
放任萨达姆侯赛因继续长期持有
Leaving Saddam Hussein in possession of weapons of mass destruction
大规模杀伤性武器是坚决不允许的"
for a few more months and years is not an option..."
你气色还可以
Well, you don't look terrible.
谢谢
Thanks.
《魔鬼女大兵》一九九七年美国军事题材影片 片中女主角参军剃了锅盖头
我以为他们会把你变成魔鬼女大兵那样
No, I mean, I thought they were gonna make you all G.I. Jane,
你懂的 没头发
you know. No hair...
- 你好 结账吧 - 好的
- Hey, could we get the check, please? - Yeah.
- 马上来 - 我只是不理解
- You got it. - I just don't know
你为什么要这么做
why you wanna do this.
是啊 我知道你不理解
Yeah, I know you don't.
今天没有其他人来了么
So, no one else came today?
没有 爸爸工作走不开 别提了
No, Dad couldn't get off work, so lay off.
不是我说他坏话
I'm not talking bad about him,
可是他还欠我两千抚养费
although he does owe me two grand in alimony.
你睡了他最好的朋友
You slept with his best friend.
- 梅根 - 所以我觉得你根本
- Megan... - So I think you're even.
梅根...
Megan...
听着 如果
Look, if...
如果你有不幸发生
If something bad was to happen,
但愿不发生这样的事 我们在通知名单上吗
God forbid, are we on the list?
我是说 那样我们就可以得到通知
I mean, just so that we would get notified?
你们在名单上
Yeah, you're on the list.
很好 那么 你父亲也在名单上吗
Okay, so then, like, with your father?
你想知道如果我死了你能得到多少抚恤金
You wanna know how much you make if I kick?
梅根 别胡说 不
Megan, don't be a shit, no, that's...
我只是对这种事没有经验
I just, I don't know how this works.
非常感谢你能来 妈
Thank you so much for coming, Mom.
宝贝 我问你是因为我没
Honey, I'm asking you because I don't...
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
- 不 谢谢 - 我没想...
- No, thanks for coming. - I didn't expect...
- 再见 我爱你 - 好吧 拜
- Bye, I love you. - Okay, bye, thank you.
爱你
Love you!
白瞎我们开了这么久的车才到这
It's not like we drove 400 hours to get here.
"给伊拉克最后的机会"
"Give Iraq one last chance."
美国海军陆战队军团
琼斯 政府车辆里允许吸烟吗
Jones, is tobacco use permitted in a government vehicle?
美国海军陆战队军团
欢迎来到海军陆战队基地
不允许 军士长
No, Master Sergeant.
圣地亚哥 加州
你的巡逻车是不是政府车辆
Is your patrol car a government vehicle?
是的 军士长
Yes, Master Sergeant.
我们能容忍失败者 废物 吊车尾吗
Do we tolerate screw-ups, losers, or laggards?
不能 军士长
No, Master Sergeant.
我们的字典里有
Do we know the meaning of the words
不会 不能 迟到 这三个词吗
won't, can't, or late?
没有 军士长
No, Master Sergeant.
巡逻队分来了三名新兵
We have three new joins assigned to the patrol section.
列兵蒂明斯 洛佩兹 利维 欢迎加入
Privates Timmins, Lopez, and Leavey, welcome aboard.
相信你们会让我们骄傲
I trust you're gonna make us all proud.
真尴尬
Whoo! It was so embarrassing.
喝酒加盐可以减轻醉意
不加盐就喝么
Are we not doing it with salt or anything?
- 不 - 认真的么
- No, no. - Seriously?
来个猛的 好吧
This is, like, hard core, okay.
耶
Yeah!
我爱这首歌
I love this song.
不
No!
- 我要再来一杯 - 你觉得咱俩...
- I need another drink. - What do you say you and I...
滚开 嘿 嘿
Back off. Hey, hey, hey.
你是我的英雄
You're my hero.
你瞅啥
Huh? What?
不 我更喜欢混蛋这个词 你还能再...
No, I prefer the term "bleeder." How much further...
bleeder有混蛋的意思 字面意思是流血的人
在俚语里引申为女人 是极具侮辱性和歧视性的词语
我喜欢 我的脚要疼死了
I love that. My feet are killing me.
真是太恶心了
That is so disgusting.
谁会穿高跟鞋去站岗
Who even wears stilettos to duty station?
去你的 我就像神奇女侠
Screw you, I'm like Wonder Woman.
好吧
Oh, yeah.
牛逼吧
What! Oh!
我本该当一名棒球手
I should have been a baseball player.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God.
我们会有麻烦的 等等
We're gonna get in trouble. Hold on.
你在干什 哦 天哪
What are you doing? Oh, God.
哇哦 真性感 我喜欢那袜子的款式
Oh, wow, that's hot. I like that sock look.
你午餐什么都没吃
You didn't have anything for lunch.
你吐的是啥
What is that?
你让我想尿裤子了
You're gonna make me pee myself,
真的 我憋不住了
seriously, I'm gonna piss myself.
- 别研究我的呕吐物了 - 我要尿了
- Stop analyzing my puke. - I'm gonna piss myself.
我去尿尿 帮我拿着
I'm gonna go pee. Hold onto that.
- 梅根 我们得快点 - 我很快的
Megan, we gotta hurry! I'll be quick.
- 嘿 - 我们还是...
- Hey! - Actually, let's...
怎么回事
What's going on?
快转身离开
Just turn around and walk.
我们没事 一切正常
We're good, we're good, it's all good.
她被抓了
Oh, they got her. It's all good.
我快好了
Um, I'm almost done.
你怎么回事 利维
What's your problem, Leavey?
对不起 军士长
Master Sergeant, I'm sorry...
闭嘴 别惹我 我不想骂人
Shut up. Don't mess with me, it brings out my Irish.
你为什么要参军海军陆战队
Why are you here in the Marines?
你不知道对吧 但我知道
You don't know, do you? Well, I do.
你以为你是第一个加入我队伍里的
You think you're the first entitled brat
自视甚高且爱惹麻烦的刺头么
with a chip on her shoulder who's come through my ranks?
这机构是为了培养英雄
This institution is for heroes, not little punks
而不是因为没有得到父母足够的关心
all screwed up in the head
就打得头破血流的不良少年
because their mommies and daddies didn't love them enough.
但是你现在身在我的兵团里
But you're in my corps now,
我希望你可以敬畏那些
and I will not see you disrespect the men and women
让海军陆战队威名远扬的士兵们
who made the Marines great!
你明白了吗
Do you understand?
是的 军士长
Yes, Master Sergeant.
再惹麻烦 我就让你卷铺盖走人
One more hiccup and I'll see you kicked out of here,
- 你听懂了么 - 是的 军士长
do you copy me? Yes, Master Sergeant.
EMI: 美军内部对违反纪律的军人的非惩罚性纠错手段
行了 给你记过处分 罚你去狗舍清理粪便
All right, you're on EMI, shit detail,
直到接到下一步通知 先休息一下
until further notice, so get some rest.
有你忙的 滚出去吧
You're gonna need it. Go on, get out of here.
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
美国海军陆战队军犬
永远忠诚
（美国海军陆战队的座右铭）
马丁军士长 这是一等兵利维
Gunny Martin, meet PFC Leavey.
今天她归你管
She's yours for the day.
利维...
Leavey...
欢迎
Welcome.
真恶心
Gross.
辛迪
好啊 辛迪 你觉得这很好笑是吧
Yeah, Cindy, I bet you think that's really funny, huh?
真恶心
Disgusting.
这是谁啊
Who's this?
雷克斯
Rex?
嘿 帅哥
Hey, you handsome boy.
妈的
Shit.
好吧
Okay!
你做完没有
You done in here?
快了 还剩两间
Uh, almost, I've got two left.
很好 外面需要你
Good, we need you outside.
坐 坐
Sit, sit.
你找到了 你找到了 好小子 过来 过来
You found it, you found it, good boy. Come here, come here.
过来 坐下 过来
Come here. Sit down, come here.
这些家伙喜欢被揉肚皮
This guy loves having his belly rubbed.
他在嗅什么
What's he sniffing out?
爆炸物
Explosives.
我们通常走在车队前面
We go in before the convoy,
嗅探路边爆破装置 确保安全
sniff out IEDs, make sure no one gets hurt.
你们也去前线
You guys on the front lines?
有时候我们在前线的前线
Sometimes we're in front of the front lines.
宙斯是一头猛兽 对吧
Zeus here is a beast, aren't ya?
他是你的么
Is he yours?
不 他属于队里所有 但是目前他归我
No, he belongs to the Corps, but he's mine for now.
你来这干嘛的 训练
What are you here for, training?
不 我清理狗舍一个星期
No, I'm cleaning out the kennels for a week.
你怎么成为训犬员的
How do you get to do that?
利维 到你了
Leavey, you up.
到我了
I'm up?
攻击
Attack!
抓住他
Get him!
嗷
Ow!
撤
Out!
- 你去牵住她 - 好 交给我
- You grab her? Yeah, I got her.
嘿 辛迪
Hey, Cindy.
好了 下士沃尔特斯 你来当指挥者
Okay, Lance Corporal Walters, you be the handler.
你还是诱饵
You're still the decoy!
让辛迪歇一会吧
Let's give Cindy a break.
- 不用 我不渴 - 操蛋吧
- Oh, no, I'm good. - Sucks, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
我一般不穿防护裤 只穿上衣
You know, I usually take the pants off, just keep the top on.
真的吗
Really?
狗知道朝着上衣咬
Dogs know to aim for the jacket.
谢谢
Thanks.
雷克斯 跟上 跟上 雷克斯
Rex, heel. Heel, Rex.
哦 糟了
Oh... Shit.
好了 这次 接近演习
Okay, this one, you approach.
他们的对话结束之后 然后开始跑 明白吗
You listen to his spiel and then start to run, okay?
如果雷克斯攻击了 你把他叫回来
If Rex attacks, you call him off.
先生 请出示身份证
Sir, I would like to see some ID.
先生 我要搜查你 如果你试图逃跑
Sir, I'm gonna search you, and if you try to run away
或者有任何过激举动
or make any sudden aggressive moves,
我训练有素的狗会攻击你
my dog is trained to attack you.
抓他 追他 追他
Get him, get him. Get him.
啊 把他弄走
Ah! Get him off!
- 把他弄走 - 撤 雷克斯 撤
Get him off! Out, Rex, out.
撤 雷克斯 撤
Out, Rex, out!
跳
Up.
好孩子 好孩子
Good boy, good boy.
天哪
Oh, gee.
你以为我会怕你
You think I'm afraid of you?
好吧
Okay.
我怕了
I am afraid of you.
别以为我不能你让也怕我
But don't think I can't make you afraid of me, too.
- 没错 我很厉害的 - 利维
- That's right, I'm a badass... - Leavey...
你还没被咬够是吗
You back for more, huh?
军士长 我怎么能成为一名训犬员呢
Gunny, how do I become a dog handler?
- 你吗 - 对
- You? - Yeah.
我到底要怎么做呢
What do I have to do exactly?
首先 停止再惹麻烦
For starters, you need to stop screwing up.
其次 你需要专家级步枪射击评分
Then, you'll need an expert rifle score,
所有科目考试九十分以上
above 90% on all your exams,
体能测试成绩为优秀
a first class PFT,
你知道谁能做到这些吗
and you know who gets those things?
那些不胡闹搅屎的人
People who aren't full of shit.
军士长 过去几天我一直在跟狗屎打交道
Gunny, I've been dealing with a lot of shit the past few days,
我可以保证 我跟狗屎可不一样
and I can assure you, I am not full of it.
好吧 这倒是让我很惊讶 因为除非我听错了
Well, that would surprise me, because unless I heard wrong,
你刚被发现在宪兵司令的办公室外撒尿
you were just found pissing outside the Provost Marshal's office.
宪兵司令
The Provost Marshal?
这绝对是胡闹搅屎的人的行为 你不觉得么
And that's definitely the act of a full-of-shit person, don't you think?
是的 军士长
Yes, Gunny.
妈蛋
Crap.
"基恩 莫纳汉 洋基队的资深教练缺席
"Gene Monahan, the Yankees' veteran trainer, is out.
似乎其中一名当班队医也缺席"
Looks like one of the doctors in attendance is out."
停火 停火 退膛 射击结束
Cease fire, cease fire, unload, all clear.
你手中掌握着别人的生死
There's lives in your hands.
是 长官 你是他的指挥者
Yes, sir. And you are the alpha.
指令由你发出 用心想清楚
It comes from you, bring it from here,
让他知道你是认真的
so he knows you mean it.
我们要再演习一遍吗
So, you want us to run it again?
我们要一直演习直到做对为止
So we gonna keep running this till we get it right.
你们要在战场拯救生命
You're gonna save lives out there.
"红袜队涌出了队员席
"And the Red Sox come pouring out of their dugout,
洋基队也离开了他们的队员席
the Yankees out of theirs.
他们在投手区混战成一团
They've all met out near the pitcher's mound in a scrum.
同时..."
Meanwhile..."
为什么你每次跑步的终点都是这
Why does your run always seem to end up here?
是吗 我没注意
Does it? I hadn't noticed.
我几周内会进行体能测试
Hey, I've got a PFT in a couple of weeks.
我在想
Just wondering,
你们准备招人么
you got any openings coming up?
谈话愉快
Good talk.
"开球 球飞向左外野
"Out of the gate, there's a fly ball deep to left,
球还在飞 终于
it's on its way, there it goes,
洋基队要进入世界棒球大赛了"
and the Yankees are going to the World Series!"
停火 停火 退膛 射击结束
Cease fire, cease fire, unload, all clear.
射手 你出师了
Shooters, your prep time has ended
五轮五发全中
with a magazine of five rounds.
我完成了晨报
I finished the morning reports.
我还需要训练员的时间表
I need the trainer's schedule, too.
- 什时候要 - 下午两点
- When do you need it by? - 1400.
- 收到 军士长 - 进来
On it, Gunny. Enter.
一等兵利维
PFC Leavey,
你能做到我还真是一点都不意外
why am I not surprised to see you in here today?
我听说你体能测试得了优秀
Yeah, I heard you got first class on your PFT,
还有专家级射击评分
and you shot expert.
- 军士长 有狗分配给我么 - 没有
- Gunny, do you have a dog for me? - No.
我说解散了么
Did I excuse you?
但是 我倒是有个铁盒子
But I do got a can, though.
你意下如何 梅森
What you say there, Mason?
她训练个铁盒子不成问题吧
Think she ready for a can?
我觉得可以 军士长
I think so, Gunny.
走吧
Carry on.
开始吧
Let's get to work.
嘿 狗不错啊
Hey, cute dog.
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
我是说 她的名字
I mean, her name.
我还没起名 我们还没过磨合期呢
I haven't named her yet, I'm waiting for us to bond.
别忘了多夸夸它
Don't forgot to use your praise voice.
好铁盒 好铁盒
Good can, good can.
至少我的铁盒听话
At least my can listens to me.
她也听我的话 你很听话对吗 宝贝
Hey, she listens to me. You listen to me, right, baby?
你听见了吗
You hear that?
听见了吗
Come on. You hear that?
早上好
Morning.
早上好 军士长
Morning, Gunny.
昨晚有人酒驾吗
Any DUIs last night?
没有 军士
No, Gunny.
很好 今天会是是很棒的一天
Good. It's gonna be a good day.
训练将会比以往更加艰难
We gonna train harder than ever before.
沃尔特斯 你昨晚干了什么
Walters, what was you doing last night?
玩光晕游戏 军士长
Playing Halo, Gunny.
你整天就干这个
That's what you do all the time?
你三周后就要出国了
You shipping out in three weeks.
关键时刻要做好战斗的准备
You better be ready to fight when it's time to fight.
- 梅森 - 是 军士长
Mason. Yes, Gunny.
你还是处男吗
Are you still a virgin?
不是 军士
No, Gunny.
你确定吗 你看起来挺像
Are you sure about that? Because you look like one.
班尼特 你昨晚和老婆通话了吗
Bennett, did you talk to your wife last night?
- 没有 军士长 - 你真以为我在乎吗
- No, Gunny. - You think I give a damn?
科莱塔  收起你那满脸堆笑
Coletta, you wipe that smile off your face.
是 军士长
Yes, Gunny.
严肃起来
Now, on a serious note,
这有一位刚从伊拉克回来的长官
I have somebody that just came back from Iraq.
他会告诉你们各种作战经验
He wants to talk to y'all about the experience,
好让你们心里有点数
so you'll know what it is.
他去过你们要去的地方
He's been where you're going,
他告诉你们的 将会拯救性命
and the things that he tells you will save lives
包括四肢
and save limbs.
这位是安德鲁 迪安中士
This is Sergeant Andrew Dean.
- 中士 请发言 - 谢谢你 军士长
- Sergeant, take the floor. - Thank you, Gunny.
- 早上好 - 早上好 中士
- Morning. - Morning, Sergeant.
准备好迎接战争了吗
Are you ready for war?
准备好了 中士
Yes, Sergeant.
你们准备的一切
Everything you've prepared for,
上过的每一节课
every lesson you've learnt,
自认为了解的每一件事
everything you think you know
踏入战场的一瞬间 都会被抛到九霄云外
will just go to shit the moment you're in country.
这些自制炸弹里面 充满了战犬们
These homemade bombs are full of crap
从没闻过的气味
that our dogs have never sniffed.
当你被困在尘暴中 狗也会被迷惑
You get caught in a sandstorm, the dogs will be confused,
他们察觉不到气味
and they won't be able to detect the odor cones.
毫不夸张地说 你们将经历腥风血雨
You're about to be running through shit's creek, literally.
负重五十磅
With 50 pounds on your back,
牵着一条狗
a dog on a leash,
努力不让自己用步枪敲打他的脑袋
trying not to smack his head in with your rifle.
你们保护的那些愚蠢的人
And the grunts that you're protecting?
他们从第一天就会恨你
Well, they'll pretty much hate you from day one.
这工作做好 拯救生命
Do this job right, you might save lives.
做不好 命丧黄泉
Do it wrong, and you'll wind up dead.
不管我形容的有多可怕
And no matter how bad I'm making it sound,
离现实还差得远呢
I'm not even coming close.
你们得让他们冷静下来
You need to keep them calm.
00:22:33,270 --> 00:22:34,855
躺下 雷克斯 躺下
Lie down, Rex, lie down.
很好
That's looking good.
- 躺下 - 情况不错
- Down. - That's looking good.
拉紧直到纱布上不起皱
Just pull so there are no wrinkles in the gauze.
在你们部署之前 这方面必须多加训练
You need to practice all of this before you deploy.
好了 现在解下皮带
Okay, let's take off the leashes.
雷克斯 不可以
Rex, no, no.
有什么问题吗
Are you having a problem over there?
没有 我可以的
No, I got this.
好孩子
Good boy.
我说解下皮带
I said take off the leash.
老兄 放轻松
Come on, buddy, just relax.
好孩子
Good boy, just relax.
你必须给他带上嘴套
You need to muzzle that dog now.
啊
Ahh!
坏狗狗
Bad dog!
该死
Shit.
该发生的总要发生
It's gonna happen when it happens.
军士长 我可以保证 伤口会很快愈合
Gunny, I'm telling you, it's gonna heal in no time.
他咬断了六根骨头  沃尔特斯
He broke six bones, Walters.
你想见我 军士
You wanted to see me, Gunny?
给你条狗
You're getting a dog.
什么
What?
你要把我的狗给她
You're giving her my dog.
- 慢着 - 他不是你的狗
- Wait. - He's not your dog.
也不是我的狗 他是海军陆战队的狗
He's not my dog. He's a Marine Corps dog.
雷克斯需要一位经验丰富的训练员
Rex needs an experienced handler.
你在挑战我的权威吗 兰斯下士
Are you questioning my authority, Lance Corporal?
她是个新手 迄今为止就训练过一只铁盒
She's a Boot. She's only trained a can so far.
别再抱怨 你他妈的可是一名陆战队员
Quit whining and act like a goddamn Marine.
你能胜任吗 快点回答
You got this? Think faster.
可以 我可以
Yeah, I got this.
很好 解散
Good, you're dismissed.
记得我吗
Remember me?
好吧 雷克斯 进洞
All right, Rex, get in the house.
进去 立刻
In the house, now.
不遵守命令不许吃饭
You're not gonna get any food unless you listen to me.
我可以陪你耗上一天 知道吗
I will stand here all day, okay?
很好 很好
Good, good.
好孩子
Good boy, stay.
呆着
Stay.
这里 找
Over here, seek.
找 找
Seek, seek.
找
Seek.
到时间了 利维
That's time, Leavey.
该死
Damn it.
五个你只找出一个
You found one out of five.
看到这家伙了吗
See this guy?
死了 死了 死了
Dead, dead, dead.
对了 还有你的狗 他也死了
Oh, and your dog, yeah, he's dead, too.
然后你的腿也炸飞了
And you blew off your legs in the process.
过来
Follow me.
再来一次
Again, Leavey.
喂 喂 过来
Hey, hey. Hey.
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
- 沿着周边走 - 他正走向桌子
- Following the perimeter. He's pulling towards the desk.
不是有一套搜索模式吗
But I thought there was a search pattern.
忘掉搜索模式 利维
Forget the search pattern, Leavey.
他在表现出了变化 看不见吗
He's showing a change, all right?
- 听他的 - 好的
- Listen to him. - Okay.
- 雷克斯 找 - 跟着他
- Rex, seek. - Follow him.
找
Okay, seek.
就是了 就是这个 他闻到气味了 提高点
That's it, that's it. He's on odor, present higher.
夸奖他 利维 夸他
Praise him, Leavey, praise him.
好孩子 好孩子 真棒
Good boy, good boy, good.
这是一只很棒的侦测犬
Okay, this is a good detection dog.
他没有任何问题
There's nothing wrong with him,
所以一定是你
so it must be you.
你哪儿做错了
What are you doing wrong?
你感受到的一切 要由皮带传达给他
Everything you feel goes down leash, okay?
一切
Everything.
你都没有把握的话 他更没有
If you're not confident, then he's not confident.
我可以把你训练的非常出色 利维 但是
I could train the heck out of you, Leavey, but...
我不能教你怎样与他相处 懂吗
I can't teach you how to bond, okay?
懂
Okay.
做的很好
Good work.
他只是很紧张
Okay, he's just nervous.
这可不是紧张
These aren't nerves.
安静
Shh!
我观察这只狗一整年了
I've been watching this dog all year.
他是我治疗过最具有攻击性的狗
He's the most aggressive dog I've ever treated.
如果不做检查他不能参与部署
He can't deploy without this exam.
我只好给他镇定剂了
I'll have to sedate him.
雷克斯 冷静点 冷静下来
Rex, calm down, calm down.
冷静
Come on.
这门必须保持关闭 知道吗
This door always stays closed, okay?
爱丽丝 塔克
Hey, Alice, Tucker.
去找 沃尔特斯
All right, go find Walters
告诉他把塔克弄干净 再一次
and tell him I want Tucker's cleaned out again.
是 中士
Yes, Sergeant.
好姑娘
Hey, good girl.
利维 把他的腿缠起来 让他知道你不害怕
Leavey, wrap his leg. Show him you're not afraid.
是的 中士
Yes, Sergeant.
雷克斯 坐 我是说
Rex, sit. I mean...
躺下
Lay down.
雷克斯 躺下
Rex, lay down.
别动
Stay.
我只是把你的爪子缠起来
I'm just gonna wrap your paw.
就...
Just...
就好了
Here you go.
很好 很好
Good, good.
如果你遇到麻烦
If you ever get into trouble,
你会希望我能知道怎么缠这个
you're gonna want me to know how to do this.
喂
Hey.
我没有...
I didn't...
我没有故意去要雷克斯
I didn't ask for Rex.
我根本没想要他
I didn't even want him.
我想要他
Yeah, well, I did want him.
所以别让他死
So, don't get him killed.
雷克斯 坐
Rex, sit.
很好
Oh, good.
我们明天就要出发了
We're shipping out tomorrow.
但我们真的还没准备好
We are so not ready for this.
但是很多人正指望着我们
But people are counting on us,
如果失败 他们会送命 所以咱们必须做好
and if we do it wrong, people die, so we gotta do it right.
好吗
Okay?
明天 下飞机的那一刻
Tomorrow, beginning the moment you step off that bird,
你们必须行动 要相信有始以来的训练
you must act, trust your training,
相信你的搭档 相信自己
trust your partner, trust yourself.
遵命
Hoo-ah!
记住
And remember,
在接下来的七个月里
everything you see, hear, taste, and touch
你们所看到的 听到的 尝到的 触碰的
over these next seven months
将会伴随你们一生
will remain with you for the rest of your lives.
要让它有价值
Make it count.
准备好了吗 利维
You okay, Leavey?
是的 就是找不到我的军刀
Yeah, I just can't find my Ka-Bar.
- 本来在我的行李... - 在你身后
- It was in my stuff and now I... - It's behind you.
谢谢
Thank you.
听着 紧张害怕没什么
Look, it's okay to be freaking out right now, all right?
很正常
It's normal.
我也有过 每个人都有
I did, everybody does.
你会没事的
You'll be fine.
你可以的
You got this.
回来的时候 给我讲讲你是如何把他们
And I wanna hear about all the asses you kicked
打成落汤鸡的
when you come back.
没有如果 只有如期而至
Not if, but when, okay?
好的
Okay.
加油
Good luck.
谢谢
Thank you.
雷克斯 安静 没事的
Rex, shh, quiet, you're fine.
让我安静几小时 利维 三十分钟就够
Hour of silence, Leavey. I'll settle for 30 minutes.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
这招对鸟很管用
It works for birds.
我明白
Hey, I know.
没事的 我明白
Hey, it's okay, I know.
你不知道我们要去哪
You don't know where we're going
对即将发生的事一无所知
or what's gonna happen when we get there.
我知道这很糟糕 但是咱们患难与共 好吗
I know it sucks, but we're in this together, okay?
好了好了 兄弟 我罩着你
It's okay. It's okay, buddy, I got you.
倒计时阶段 十分钟后落地
We're on final, be on the ground in 10.
收拾装备 系好安全带 准备降落
Get your gear together, strap in. Get ready for landing.
没问题
All right.
听好了 马里恩和彼得斯在哪
Okay, listen up. Where's Marion and Peters?
长官
Sir.
你们的车在那
Your vehicles are right over there.
你们去珀迪塔营地
You're going to Camp Perditha.
- 利维和琼斯 - 在
- Leavey, Jones. - Yeah.
护卫队在那边等你们
Your convoy's waiting for you right over there.
你们去拉马迪营地 剩下的跟我来
You're going to Camp Ramadi. The rest of you, follow me.
别忘了 不管多糟
Hey, don't forget, no matter how bad it gets,
至少不用牵着铁盒去闻炸弹
you could have been out there sniffing bombs with a tin can.
的确是
True.
保重
Be safe.
- 好的 - 好吗
- Okay. - All right?
祝你狩猎成功
Hey, good hunting.
回见 白痴们
See you later, idiots.
再见
Adios!
拉马迪营地
安巴尔省
至少咱们还有个单间 是吧
At least we got a single, right?
有时候做女生还挺好
Sometimes it actually pays to be a girl.
别害怕
Don't be scared.
嘿
Hey.
太棒了
Oh, great.
到了伊拉克才露出你那调皮本性
You wait to get to Iraq to find your inner puppy.
上来 上来
Up, up, up, up.
好孩子
Good boy, good boy.
真是个好孩子
Yes, that's a good boy, good boy.
好孩子 好孩子
Good boy, good boy, yeah, yeah.
真是好孩子
That's a good boy.
放松点 新兵
Relax, Boot.
这次是进攻战 不是防守战
It's outgoing, not incoming.
我说的对吧  奇科
Ain't that right, Chico, huh?
多谢
Thanks.
洗浴时间
男性
女性
洗浴时间
男性
女性
洗浴时间
男性
女性
洗浴时间
男性
女性
洗浴时间
男性
女性
洗浴时间
男性
女性
别看了 老兄
Settle down. Come on, man.
进去
Let's go.
快进去
Yeah, move it along.
快点行不行
Hurry it up, all right?
开学第一天 老弟
First day of school, bud.
祝我好运
Wish me luck.
洗澡用的沐浴球
礼品店里一定有卖丝瓜络的
I'm pretty sure they sell loofahs in the gift shop.
不对 礼品店被炸了
Actually, no, they bombed the gift shop.
真遗憾 我喜欢丝瓜络
Well, that's too bad. I like loofahs.
我是马特莫拉莱斯 你今天的导游
I'm Matt Morales. I'll be your tour guide today.
梅根 利维 他叫什么
Megan Leavey. Who's that?
他叫 奇科  奇科 坐
This is Chico. Chico, sit.
我训练 奇科如何把敌人舔死
I trained Chico to lick the enemy to death.
很好
Nice.
- 你从哪来 - 纽约
- So, where are you from? - New York.
是吗 我也是
Ah, yeah? Me, too.
你应该不是洋基队的粉丝吧
You're not a Yankees fan, though, right?
死忠粉
Born and bred.
不会吧
Oh, come on.
扎心了 来真的吗
Dagger to my heart, really?
估计这是咱俩最后一次对话了 梅根
Well, I guess we'll never speak again, Megan.
奇科 我们才不和洋基队粉丝说话呢
Chico, we don't talk to Yankees fans, right?
好狗狗
Good boy.
这是莫拉莱斯下士
This is Corporal Morales.
莫拉莱斯 这是利维下士
Morales, Lance Corporal Leavey.
莫拉莱斯会送你到二号入口检查站
Morales will drop you at the ECP,
然后他要去萨德尔城
then he's off to Sadr City,
另一支队伍到达之前
so you'll be on your own
一切就靠你自己了
till we can get another team out there.
尽量别让你的狗太兴奋
Just try and keep your dog from overheating.
好的
Okay.
上一个女训员把内裤放在了椒盐酥饼里
Last female handler got her panties in a pretzel
因为我们不允许女生参加任务 只留在检查点
'cause we don't allow girls on missions, just checkpoints.
对你来说成问题吗
That gonna be a problem with you?
- 完全不 - 很好
- Not at all. - Good.
解散
Dismissed.
酥饼里的内裤
"Panties in a pretzel."
还以为你不和我说话了
Thought we weren't talking anymore.
其实 我刚刚是自言自语
Well, I was talking to myself right there,
但是 再给你一次机会吧
but, you know, I'll give you another chance,
如果你再提洋基队一个字 我们就绝交
and if you mention the Yankees again, we're done.
参谋军士贾维斯倒是个挺有魅力的人
Staff Sergeant Jarvis is a real charmer, though.
上周他告诉我他喜欢我这种人
Last week he told me he always liked my people.
我爸是波多黎各人 我妈是斯堪的纳维亚人
My dad's Puerto Rican, my mom's Scandinavian.
你猜他说的是哪种人
Who do you think he was talking about, huh?
一定是斯堪的纳维亚人
The Scandinavians, obviously.
我也是这么想的
Right, that's what I thought.
准备好战斗
保持一百米的距离 否则格杀勿论
第一个月
欢迎来到狗屎之都
Welcome to the capital of shit.
这些狗是怎么回事
What's with all the dogs?
流浪狗 满身病菌 别让你的狗接近他们
Strays, full of diseases. Keep 'em away from your dog.
必要的话就开枪
Shoot 'em if you have to.
你需要知道接下来这些事
Here's all you need to know.
他们下车后再进行搜查
Don't search till they're out of the car.
确保打开他们的所有物品
Make sure they open everything.
记住 伊拉克人 不喜欢狗
Remember, Iraqis, they don't like dogs.
这是他们的宗教教义
It's in their religious teachings,
所以肯定也不会喜欢我们的狗
and they damn sure don't like ours.
抓到训犬员是有赏金的
There's a bounty on canine handlers
抓到女训犬员更是大大有赏
and an even bigger bounty on female canine handlers.
也就是说他们可能会直接杀了你
Which means they'll probably wanna kill you.
除非他们想强奸你
Well, actually, unless they wanna bone you.
不然就是先奸后杀
Or they might wanna bone you and then kill you.
如果有人掏出手机 嘣 你死了
And if one of them pulls out a cell phone, boom, you're dead.
除此之外 还是挺轻松的
Aside from that, it's pretty chill.
讲真的 机灵点
Seriously, be smart,
时刻留意四周 提高警惕
keep your head on a swivel, heightened awareness.
知道了
Okay.
二号入口检查站
拉马迪政府中心
走 走 走 排队去
Go, go, go, get to the line.
开心点
You need to have fun.
别抱怨 老兄
No complaints, bro.
回见
See ya.
别停 一直走
Hey, keep everybody moving.
琼斯 把卡车挪走
Jones, move his truck.
雷克斯 喝水吗
Rex, you want some water?
班迪尼 让那家伙关掉引擎
Bandini, tell that guy to cut his engine.
关掉引擎
Turn your engine off.
走 快走
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
问他出行原因
Ask him the reason for traveling today.
我去巴达格做生意
I'm heading to Baghdad for business.
你会说英语
You speak English.
对 这样对生意有好处
Yes, better for business.
关掉引擎
Hey! Cut your engine off.
我让你把那个车的引擎关掉
I told you to turn that bike off.
把衬衫撩起来
Lift your shirts.
快点儿 转过去 快
Come on, turn around, come on.
利维 排查车子
Leavey, clear the car.
请把后备箱打开 先生
Open the trunk please, sir.
上帝啊 班迪尼
Jesus, Bandini.
我让你把那个车的引擎关掉
I told you to turn that bike off.
起来 起来
Get up, get up.
站到这里 撩起衬衫
Stand over here. Lift your shirt.
的确 对生意有好处
Damn straight, better for business.
后退
Stay back.
你想让我下次直接射杀你吗 把车子扶起来
You want me to shoot you next time? Pick your bike up.
但是 别碰它
Don't touch it, though.
别动
No.
来
Come here.
安全
Clear.
他叫什么名字
What is his name?
孩子 来这儿问问题
Hey, kid, we ask the questions here.
先生 请你开车前往检查站
Sir, could you get in the vehicle and proceed to the checkpoint?
他叫雷克斯
His name is Rex.
这边
Here,
请收下我的名片 我是做游戏机的
let me give you my card, X-box.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
- 马上退回车内 - 雷克斯
- Back in your vehicle now. - Rex!
放松
Come on.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你不能告诉任何伊斯兰教徒你的狗的名字
You never tell a Haji your dog's name.
他只是个孩子
He's just a kid.
我可见过一个没比他大多少的孩子
Yeah, and I've seen kids not much older
手里拿着炸药叫一只狗到他身边
call a dog over with a detonator in hand.
你想让你的狗好好活着吗 管好你的嘴
You wanna keep your dog alive? Sort your crap out.
我们走
Hey, let's go.
下一个
Next.
让这些人都动起来 快 快
Keep these people moving. Let's go, let's go!
一切都会变好的 我保证
We'll get better at this, I promise.
好孩子
Good boy.
- 找 - 你确定吗
- Seek. - You sure?
- 好吧 - 这是什么
- All right. - Oh, what is it?
你找到了
You did it.
好孩子 好孩子 来 来
Good boy, good boy, come on, come on.
找 来
Seek, come on.
马上凑成清一色了 看看
Could be a full suit. Check it out.
- 好孩子 好孩子 - 他找到了吗
- Good boy, good boy. - Did he find it?
他们休息过吗
Those guys ever take a break?
- 没有 - 来这边
- No. - Come here.
我想也是
I guess so.
好孩子
Good boy.
你想玩一会儿 孩子 你想玩一会儿 去吧
You wanna play, boy? You wanna play? Go get it.
好孩子 雷克斯 来这边 雷克斯
Good boy, Rex. Come here, Rex.
利维 侦察队需要你去执行任务
Leavey, Recon needs you on a mission,
五分钟内赶到
five minutes.
我以为我不能执行任务
I thought I wasn't allowed to go on missions.
没有其他的人选了 带上装备
There's no one else. Get your gear.
拉马迪东部
第三个月
哟
Yo.
他们炸死了我们五个人 我们进去好好查一下
They blew up five of our guys. Let's get in there and smoke them out.
你们中的一个人排查路况 房子在这边
One of you check the road. The house is over here.
我排查路况 房子归你
I'll take the road. You get the houses.
好 检查下狗 他们肚子里可能会埋爆破装置
Okay, hey, sweep the dogs. They might be stuffed with IEDs.
安全
Clear.
我只希望这家伙有几条大毛毯
I just wish this guy had a couple rugs.
问他为什么有这么多毛毯
Ask him why so many rugs?
- 这些是祈祷用的拜毯 - 问他
- They're prayer rugs. - Ask him.
他们是宗教家庭
They're a religious family.
他们不是我们政府的敌人
They're not enemies of the States.
他们感激我们在与反叛者的
And they thank Americans for helping
斗争中施以援手
in the fight against insurgents.
谢谢你说的这些屁话
Oh, we thank you for your bullshit.
打开橱柜
Hey, open this cabinet.
打开
Open it!
后退
Get back.
他发现了什么 他有发现吗
What's he got? He got something?
给我们一点空间 退后
We need some room, step back.
把这些毯子移开
Move these rugs.
他儿子把它们放在这儿的
His sons put 'em there.
我们不在乎
We don't care.
移开
Move them!
他身体不好
He's not a well man.
告诉这个好兄弟我们不关心他的健康
Tell habibi we don't care about his health
- 他需要把这些挪开 - 好 好 好
- and he needs to move them. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
现在就挪开
Move them now.
现在
Today!
- 好 需要一个人检查一下那边 - 我来
- Okay, gonna need someone to check that. - I got it.
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
不许动 不许动
Don't move! Don't move!
站住
Hey! Stop!
Stop!
不许动 不许动
Don't move! Don't move!
干得漂亮 比我们快多了
Nice work, cleared out quicker than we found it.
好嘞 厄运连连啊
All right. More bad luck.
看看啊
Look at this.
这是你的杰作
This is you?
是他的
Well, it's him.
现在别冲着我得意忘形
Well, don't get all big-headed on me now.
天 你可是刚刚救下了许多条人命
Shit, you just saved a bunch of lives.
完成得很出色 你们两个
Outstanding work. Both of you.
谢谢
Thank you.
走吧  奇科
Come on, Chico.
三 二 一
Three, two, one.
你作弊
You cheated!
我赢了
I won!
我赢了 我赢了
I won! I won!
没事 他们很好 他们很好
It's okay, they're fine, they're fine.
- 我们吓到他了 -  奇科
- Yeah, we shook 'em up. - Chico.
老手啊 我早就知道那是什么牌了
Oh, you're slick, 'cause I already know what card that is.
接着来 多选几张
There we go, pick up some more.
继续 你还是没拿到那张牌
Keep going, you still don't have it.
- 我的天 - 继续
- Oh, my God. - Keep going.
- 继续 - 放轻松
- Keep going. - Relax.
他看起来就像真的在苦恼
He looks like he's actually trying to decide
应该先吃我身体的哪一部分
which of my body parts he wants to eat first.
的确
Yeah, he is.
哦
Oh!
- 终于等到这一刻 - 嗯哼
- The moment has come. - Mmm-hmm.
你挖好陷阱等我跳
You set that up.
我可没有
Totally didn't.
- 很机智啊 - 谢谢夸奖
- That was good. - Thank you.
那么 大都会球迷
So, Mets fan,
你打过棒球吗
did you ever play?
打过 在高中 三垒
I did, high school, third base.
我自认为打的相当不错
I thought I was actually pretty good,
但是大学球探不这么认为
but college scouts disagreed,
我就到了这里
so here I am.
去他们的
Screw 'em,
我真不是坐在教室好好学习的那类乖宝宝
I'm not really a sit-in-the-classroom kind of guy anyway.
我也不是
Me neither.
说说你的故事
So, what's your story?
你为什么来参军
Why'd you join?
我想离我原来操蛋的生活远一点
I wanted to get the fuck away from my life.
真挺扫兴的
That was a downer.
杰西是不是也是原因之一
Does it have anything to do with Jesse?
我看到了你的纹身
I saw your tattoo.
嗯...
Um...
没错
Yeah.
我是说 他曾是我最好的朋友
I mean, he was my best friend.
我们曾在他的房子里共度每一个周末
We used to spend every weekend at his house.
我是说 不是你想的那样 我们是...
I mean, not like that. We were...
他就像我的哥哥
He was like my brother.
他的家人们都很棒
His family was amazing,
不像我的
unlike mine.
我在他们家过圣诞
I spent Christmases there,
一个周末 我们喝酒 吸毒
and one weekend we were drinking and taking pills,
做那些高中生才会做的蠢事
doing stupid high school stuff,
我们吸了相同的量
and we took the exact same amount.
我可能比他吸得还要多 但是...
I mean, I probably took even more than he did, but...
我醒了 他没有
Well, I woke up. He didn't.
他的家人一直试着联系我
His family keep trying to reach out,
但是我甚至不能...
but I can't even...
死的应该是我 我们心知肚明
It should have been me, and we all know it.
我明天得早起
I gotta get up early.
我要去睡觉了
I'm gonna go to sleep.
- 晚安 - 晚安
- Good night. - Night.
好孩子 好孩子
Good boy, good boy.
我们需要一支搜查犬队来排查道路和附近地区
We need one dog team for a road sweep and surrounding area check.
但是你之前要求的是两支
But you requested two teams.
计划赶不上变化
Things change.
我们只能装下一支队伍
We only have the room for one team.
这次需要精准控制狗链 还是我去吧
Hey, it's going down leash. I'll go.
利维
Leavey.
我可以的
I got this.
列队
Line up!
听到了吗 我们走
You heard him, let's go.
动起来
Move it.
阿尔布阿萨夫 拉马迪以西十公里
第六个月
你是纽约来的
You're from New York?
对
Yeah.
我也是
Me, too.
我第一次上战场
My first time in country.
他呢
What about him?
德国来的
Germany.
德国牧羊犬 我喜欢
German shepherd, I like that.
你知道我听说了什么吗
You know what I heard?
我听说敌军喜欢偷狗 对吗
I heard the enemy likes to steal the dogs, right?
在他们身上捆上炸弹
Strap bombs on them,
然后把他们还给原主人
send them back to their owner.
鉴于雷克斯能用他的牙咬断一个人的胳膊
Well, since Rex can break someone's arm with his teeth,
我不是太担心
I'm not too worried.
利维 带着狗上场吧
Leavey, dog up.
没事
It's okay.
他们待在一起很长时间了
They've been spending a lot of time together.
我很高兴我不是他们
I'm glad I'm not them.
别说话
Stop talking!
好孩子 好孩子
Good boy, good boy.
有发现了
Found something!
利维 他真的需要再休息一次吗
Hey, Leavey, does he really need another break?
恕我直言 已经两个小时了
With all due respect, it's been two hours,
现在是四十九摄氏度 所以 他需要
and it's 120 degrees, so yeah, he does.
这是他应得的
It's not like he hasn't earned it.
有车辆靠近
Vehicle approaching.
架枪
Guns up.
雷克斯
Rex.
戈麦斯 鸣枪警告 第一轮
Gomez, warning shot, one round.
他没有减速
He's not slowing.
准备开火
Stand by to light him up.
戈麦斯 奥康纳 拿下那个伊斯兰教徒
Gomez, O'Connor, secure the Haji.
趴下 趴下
Get on the ground, get on the ground.
趴下
Get on the ground.
立刻趴下 趴下
Get on the ground now, get on the ground.
在地上躺平
Lay flat on the ground now.
手放在背后
Put your hands behind your back.
Hands behind your back.
雷克斯
Rex!
安全
Clear!
利维 排查车辆
Leavey, check the vehicle.
来 我们走
Hey, come on, let's go.
好 好
Okay, okay.
雷克斯 雷克斯
Rex, Rex!
雷克斯 不 不 不
Rex, no, no, no.
雷克斯
Rex.
我不会丢下我的狗
I'm not leaving without my dog.
走啊 走啊
Come on, come on.
嘿
Hey!
你的狗怎么会漏掉了那个呢
How did your dog miss that?
我们所有人都可能因此丧命
You could have got us all killed.
我从未见过埋得这么深的爆破装置
I never seen an IED buried this deep.
你来看看
You gotta see this.
他们肯定是从那些房子那里引爆炸弹的
They must have triggered the bomb from those houses.
我不知道 或许他们的目标是雷克斯
I don't know, maybe they were targeting Rex.
不 他们的目标是利维和雷克斯
No, they were targeting Leavey and Rex.
让我们抓住那些胆小鬼们
Let's get those cowards.
给莫拉莱斯发无线电
Radio Morales,
让他和他的狗马上赶过来
get him and his dog down here now.
不行 如果等到莫拉莱斯来
No, if we wait for Morales,
那些观测手早就逃走了
the spotters will be gone by then.
- 我们可以做到 - 不可能 别想了
- We can do it. - No way, forget it.
你看到我们今天发现了多少爆破装置吗
Do you see how many IEDs we found today?
没有我们 你要怎样安全穿过旷野
How are you gonna make it through the field without us?
天啊 利维 你受伤了
God damn it, Leavey, you're injured.
对 因为那些混蛋们一整天都在监视我们
Yeah, because those assholes waited all day watching us.
她有些脑震荡 中士
She's got a concussion, Sergeant.
她可能有点糊涂 丧失判断力了
She may be confused, disoriented.
他们差点就杀了我们
They almost killed us.
没有我们
How are you gonna make it
你们要怎样安全穿过旷野和那片房子
through the field and the house without us?
你的狗怎么办 他也受伤了
What about your dog? He's injured, too.
他很好
He's fine.
我们可以做到
We can do this.
走
Let's go!
我联系一下空中支援
I'm gonna check with Air Support.
与此同时 戈麦斯 集合
In the meantime, Gomez, get your team together.
抵达 排查 动作要快
Get in there, check it out, do it fast.
- 我们在这里掩护你 - 是的 长官
- We'll cover you from here. - Yes, sir.
上 你们还在等什么 动起来 动起来
Go, what are you waiting for? Move, move!
第一间房
The first house,
距离一百五十米
150 meters.
有一点儿太安静了 你拿主意吧
It's a little too quiet, but it's up to you.
我们时间不多
We don't have all day.
我们跟着你走 利维
We'll follow you, Leavey.
移动
Let's move out.
他又发现了一个
He found another one?
对
Yeah.
是压力盘
It's a pressure plate.
好孩子 找
Good boy. Seek.
好 利维 我们为你准备好了
Okay, Leavey, we're ready for you.
安全
Clear!
- 利维 该你了 - 找
- Leavey, you're up. - Seek.
这是一所学校
This is a school.
真是一团糟
That's messed up.
找
Seek.
好了 利维
Okay, Leavey.
妈的
Whoa, shit...
看起来他们刚走没多久
Looks like they were just here.
中奖了
Jackpot.
哇哦 哇哦 哇哦
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
利维 利维 利维
Leavey, Leavey, Leavey!
没事儿
Hey. It's okay.
- 是戈麦斯 - 你想让我做什么
- It's Gomez. - What do you want me to do?
我不知道 哪里不太对劲
I don't know, something's not right.
他刚刚被炸伤了 我不知道发生了什么
He just got blown up, man. I don't know what's going on.
利维 我要走了 我要走了
Leavey, I gotta move, I gotta move.
趴下
Get down!
约翰逊 约翰逊
Johnson, Johnson!
动起来 快动起来
Move it! Let's move!
我们得离开这
We gotta move!
等等
Wait!
掩护 移动
Covering, move!
快 我们走
Come on. Let's go.
约翰逊
Johnson!
快 快 快 快
Go, go, go, go!
快走 快走
Let's go, let's go.
控制火力 说话 伙计们 说话
Suppress the fire, let's talk, boys, talk.
我想听到有人说话
I wanna hear talk!
瞄准射击 瞄准射击
Point and shoot, point and shoot.
动起来 动起来
Move it, move it.
利维 利维
Leavey, Leavey!
约翰逊 约翰逊 走
Johnson, Johnson, go!
我们必须动起来
We gotta move!
快 快 快
Go, go, go.
动起来
Move!
奥康纳 奥康纳
O'Connor, O'Connor.
掩护 移动
Covering. Move!
移动 移动
Move, move!
移动 约翰逊
Move, Johnson!
掩护 移动
Covering, move!
快 利维 利维 移动
Go, Leavey, Leavey, move!
动起来 动起来
Moving, moving!
快走 快走 快走
We gotta go, let's go, let's go!
控制火力 右翼 动起来 伙计们
Suppressing fire, right flank. Let's move, boys.
给他们点颜色瞧瞧
Light 'em up.
快走 快走
Let's go, let's go!
快走 动起来 动起来
Let's go, move it, move it.
快 快 快走
Come on, come on, let's go.
掩护
Covering!
施里纳 利维和戈麦斯在哪儿
Shriner, where's Leavey, Gomez?
约翰逊 移动
Johnson, move!
掩护 移动
Covering, move!
利维 准备好了吗
Leavey, ready?
快 快走 快走
Come on, let's go, let's go.
- 快走 快走 - 好
- Let's go, let's go. - Okay.
快
Hurry up.
温切斯特步枪弹药不足了
Winchester running low on ammo.
- 快 快 快 - 等一下
- Go, go, go. - Wait.
快走 快走 进来
Let's go, let's go, get in.
动起来 动起来 利维
Move it, move it, Leavey.
戈麦斯 快点 进来
Gomez, come on, get in.
利维
Leavey!
停
Stop.
她好像没上来
I think she didn't make it.
- 她没上来 - 马上停车
- She didn't make it! - Hold it right now.
没事 没事
It's okay, it's okay.
我没事 我没事 我没事
I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay.
右翼 在那儿
On the right flank, right there.
她没上来
She didn't make it.
- 停车 - 利维
- Hold it. - Leavey!
- 快走 快走 - 动起来 动起来
- Let's go, let's go. - Move it, move it.
- 我们要走 - 等等
- We're leaving. - Wait!
减速 减速 她没进来
Slow down, slow down, she's not in.
好了 我们走 我们走
Okay, let's go, let's go.
- 没错 我们接到她了 - 走 快走
- Yeah, we got her. - Move, move!
利维 你需要尽快用救护直升飞机运送
Leavey, you're Medevac ASAP.
嘿 我会照顾他的 好吗
Hey, I'll take care of him, okay?
我保证
I promise.
听着
Listen to me.
出任务的本该是我
It should have been me, all right?
这里是从拉马迪起飞的直升机零九号
This is helo zero niner departing Ramadi with one wounded
搭载一名伤员前往巴格达医院途中 完毕
en route to Baghdad hospital, over.
好了 下士
Okay, Corporal.
你的鼓膜破裂 所以出现听力下降
Uh, you've got ruptured eardrums, so hearing loss
甚至短暂失忆都很正常
and even short-term memory loss are gonna be normal,
但你能完全康复
but you should fully recover.
- 我的狗在哪里 - 他没事
- Where's my dog? - He's okay.
他很好 他在布卢戴蒙德
He's fine, he's at Blue Diamond.
- 我要见他  - 不行 不行
- I need to see him. - Oh, no, no.
下士 不行 躺下
Uh-uh, Corporal, no, no. Lay down.
他没事的 他很好
He's okay, he's fine.
重要的是我们会照顾你 确保你没事
The important thing is we look after you, make sure you're okay.
顺便告诉你一声 下士
And just so you know, they're sending you home
三周后他们会送你回家过圣诞节
for Christmas, Corporal, three weeks,
然后带你到彭德尔顿接受康复训练
then back to Pendleton for training and rehab,
等你回到基地 会见到你的狗的 好吗
and you'll see your dog when you get back to base, okay?
我们通知了她的长官 他知道发生了什么
Uh, we notified her commander, so he's aware of what's going on.
爸爸
Dad.
你回来了我很高兴 你还好吗
I'm glad you're home. You okay?
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
你看起来不错
You look good.
好吧
Okay.
我圣诞节要工作
I gotta work on Christmas.
没关系 爸爸
It's okay, Dad.
- 你确定 - 是的
- You sure? - Yeah.
- 你没事吧 - 没事
- You're okay? - Yeah.
她可能不希望我...
She'd probably rather if I didn't...
是的 我知道
Yeah. I know.
靠近那里 所以
Go near there, so...
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
Yeah, Merry Christmas.
- 我爱你 - 我爱你
- I love you. - I love you.
谢天谢地 你没事
Thank God you're okay.
再见了
Bye, you.
你确定你没事吧
You're sure you're okay with that?
- 嗯 我能搞定 - 好吧
- Yeah, I got it. - All right.
- 谢谢 - 好
- Thank you. - Yeah.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
嗨 宝贝
Hi, baby.
嘿 妈妈
Hey, Mom.
我很抱歉 但我...
Okay, I am sorry, but I'm just...
你说雷克斯还没回来是什么意思
What do you mean Rex isn't back yet?
他一周前就该回来了 每次我打电话
He was supposed to be back a week ago, and every time I call,
对方都说他很快就会回来
someone says that he's gonna be back soon,
他很快就会回来
he's gonna be back soon.
我有点糊涂
I'm just a little bit confused.
我只是告诉你我知道的 下士...
I'm just telling you what I know, Corporal...
还有 请别再打过来了
And please, don't call again.
我一有消息会立刻通知你的 好吗
I'll let you know as soon as I have something to report, okay?
好吧 等一下 如果有人可以...
Okay, wait just one second. If somebody could just...
这太棒了 宝贝
This is wonderful, honey.
你看到了吗 梅根
Did you see this, Megan?
噢 简直太棒了
Oh! This is wonderful.
宝贝 这是给你的
Here, honey, this is for you.
谢谢 妈妈
Thank you, Mom.
我本来想多给你几件的 宝贝
I would have liked to get you more, honey,
但是美容店排队很慢 所以...
but the salon's been slow so...
没关系
That's okay.
所以 我就选了它 宝贝
So, that's the one, honey.
你肯定想象不到我有多开心
I'm, like, so happy, you can't even imagine.
彭德尔顿营地 加州
再跟威尔金斯确认一下 好吗
Just double check with Wilkins, all right?
是的 长官
Yes, sir, will do.
- 雷诺兹
- Reynolds?
嘿 我是利维下士
Hey, I'm Corporal Leavey.
- 利维 - 没错
- Leavey? - Yeah.
哇
Wow.
你知道自己在电话里有点咄咄逼人吧
You do know your phone style is a bit aggressive, right?
其实 我不这样认为
Actually, I don't think she does.
- 嘿 - 你好 利维
- Hey. - Hey, what's up, Leavey?
- 嗨 - 你还好吗
- Hi. - How you doing?
- 没事吧 - 没事 我很好
- You all right? - Yeah, I'm okay.
我听说你出任务的时候有点慌张
I heard you got a little rattled up out there.
- 一切还好吗 - 我很好
- Everything okay? - I'm fine.
你什么时候回来的
When did you get back?
上周
Uh, last week.
我就来几天 然后就回去了
I'm just here for a couple days, then I'm going back.
雷克斯怎么样了 他在哪
How's Rex? Where is he?
我不知道 我有一阵子没见到他了
I don't know. I haven't seen him in a while.
他还好吗
Is he okay?
我不知道他好不好
I don't know how he is,
但是没有他的日子我很颓废
but I've been crap without him.
是的 我无法想象
Yeah, yeah, I can't imagine.
我从来没离开布鲁诺超过十二小时
I haven't left Bruno for what, 12 hours?
谁是好孩子 布鲁诺
Who's a good boy, Bruno?
好的 长官 我会告诉她的
Yes, sir, I'll tell her.
嘿 要是你愿意 你也可以去抱你的狗了
Hey, you can go and cuddle, too, if you like.
雷克斯刚被送到门口
Rex just pulled up to the gate.
- 布鲁诺, 布鲁诺. - 再见 长官
- Bruno, Bruno. - Bye, sir.
好的
All right.
嗨
Hey, hi!
过来 好孩子
Come here, come here, good boy.
小心 小心
Careful, careful.
好孩子 很好 太好了
Good boy, good, hi, good.
好孩子
Oh! Good boy.
没事了
Okay.
好孩子 好孩子 好孩子
Good boy, good boy, good boy, good boy, good boy.
很好
Good.
很好 加油
Good, good, come on.
来 停下 这边
Come on, stop, this way.
雷克斯 来 没事的
Rex, come, it's okay.
嘿 怎么了
Hey, what's going on?
他们说我不需要穿裤子
They told me I didn't need the bottoms.
没错 除非你不想要
Yeah, well that depends on how much you like keeping
你那两瓣屁股了
both halves of your ass.
把裤子穿上
Keep them on.
哈哈
Ha-ha!
你们真有意思
You guys are very funny!
没事 慢一点 慢一点 慢一点
Okay, slow down, slow down, slow down,
这只是花而已 没事的
it's just some flowers, it's okay.
给你买了些花
因为丝瓜络都卖光了
这是...
It's...
讽刺的是 他们最后发现丝瓜络有货
The crazy part, then they ended up having loofahs,
但他们说单买一个不送货
but they said they couldn't deliver a loofah.
太贴心了 真的很贴心
It was sweet, that's really sweet.
花我也很喜欢
I mean, I like flowers, too.
那就好 但如果是丝瓜络 是吧
Cool, but the loofah would have been, come on.
是的 那会更有趣
That would have been funnier, yeah.
- 丝瓜络效果更佳 对吧 - 没错
- The loofah would have worked, right? - Yeah, yeah.
我知道...
I know. Um...
那么 嗨
So, hi.
- 嗨 - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
哇 你真的很壮
Wow, you're really strong.
简直像大学的床 宿舍的床
They're like college beds, like dorm room beds.
- 糟透了 - 是的
- It's awful. - Yeah.
好消息是你可能不需要
Well, the good news is you probably don't have
再付酒钱了
to pay for drinks anymore
现在你是战争英雄了 你很重要
now that you're a war hero and everything.
你觉得我是个英雄
You think I'm a hero?
大家都这么说
Well, that's the word on the street.
那么你最近都在忙些什么 有什么新闻吗
So what have you been up to? What's going on?
大部分时间在理疗 这是最糟的
Um, mostly just physical therapy. It's the worst.
我的护士绝对是女巫转世 理疗过程很无趣
The nurse is an absolute witch, so that's not fun.
- 是吗 - 是的
- Ai! - Yeah.
那么 哪里痛 伤到哪里了
So, what hurts? Where does it hurt?
主要是头部
Mostly my head.
背和脖子
My back, my neck,
我还觉得...
and I just...
炸弹好像震裂了我的脚背
It feels like the bomb blew out my arches.
- 所以几乎全身都是伤 - 嗯
- So everywhere. - Mmm-hmm.
好吧 那你不能再穿高跟鞋了
Well, no more high heels for you.
我知道 我对此很失望
I know, so bummed about that.
把你的脚给我
Hey, let me get your foot.
让我来施点魔法
Let me do some magic.
- 按摩吗 - 没错
- A massage? - Yeah.
因为你是英雄
Just 'cause you're a hero.
我真幸运
Lucky me.
英雄可以享受按摩
Heroes get massages.
我应该多被炸几次
I should get exploded more often.
是啊 我应该经常飞回来
Yeah, I should fly back more often.
你的雷克斯 他怎么样了
How's your boy, Rex, doing?
他很好
He's good.
他好多了 只不过好的有点慢
He's doing better, it's just slow.
估计再过几周 我就能和他
I think that I'm gonna be able to start training with him again
重新开始训练了
in a couple weeks.
嗯
Hmm.
你要待多久
How long do I have you for?
那看情况
Well, that depends.
你希望我待多久
How long do you want me for?
我很年轻 我的家人都能活到八十多岁
I'm a young man, we live into our 80s in my family.
我爸妈离婚了
Yeah, we get divorced in mine.
或许 我会考虑为你破个例
I could possibly make an exception, though,
如果你能一下子变成一个洋基队球迷
if you were all of a sudden, say, a Yankees fan,
看很多场洋基队的比赛
went to a lot of Yankees games.
太过分了 这个要求太过分了
That's a lot, you see, that's a lot to ask for.
是啊 我想也是
Yeah, that's what I thought.
我是认真的
I'm being serious.
我也是
Well, so am I.
我不相信什么天长地久
I don't do the whole forever and ever thing.
听着 相信我 通常我也不会
Look, trust me, neither do I, usually.
好了 别这么严肃
Okay, well, so stop being so serious.
我们还是... 我们还是亲热一会吧
Let's just...Let's just make out.
检查 二十分钟之后
Inspection, 20 minutes.
- 这简直... - 别说话
- This is... - Don't say anything.
- 我们会惹上麻烦的 对吧 - 是的
- We could get in trouble, though, right? - Yes.
我觉得我们应该换个地方
I think we should relocate...
但不是现在
But not now.
全体 立正
Detail, attention.
很遗憾地通知你们 安德鲁 迪安
I'm sorry to inform you that Andrew Dean,
安德鲁 迪安中士
Sergeant Andrew Dean,
于昨日十五点三十七分死于自杀式炸弹袭击
was killed by a suicide bomber at 1537 yesterday.
他曾试图阻止爆炸的发生 但没能赶上
He tried to stop him, but he couldn't in time.
布鲁诺幸存了下来
Bruno survived.
被发现的时候布鲁诺用身体护住了他
They found Bruno lying on top of him.
安德鲁 迪安是一名出色的海军陆战队士兵
Andrew Dean was a good Marine,
他也是一个好人
and he was a very good man.
愿上帝保佑他
God bless his soul.
布鲁诺 起来 布鲁诺, 布鲁诺
Bruno, up, Bruno, Bruno.
布鲁诺 过来 孩子 来 起来
Bruno, here boy, here, up.
布鲁诺 起来 布鲁诺 布鲁诺 这里
Bruno up, Bruno, Bruno, here boy.
布鲁诺 来 布鲁诺
Bruno, here, Bruno.
他在找他
He's looking for him.
他是不会放弃的
He'll never stop.
有时我们意识不到
Sometimes we don't realize,
他们是我们的家人 我们也是他们的家人
as much as they our family, we theirs, too.
来吧 加油 加油
Come on, come on, come on. Come on, come on, come on.
别这样 宝贝
Come on, baby.
好了 来 再试一次 我们再试一次
Okay, come on, gonna try again. Let's try again.
准备好了吗
Ready? Ready?
雷克斯 来
Rex, come.
加油 加油
Come on, come on.
快点 加油
我知道
I know.
没事的
It's okay.
雷克斯 雷克斯
Rex, Rex.
没事的
Hey, it's okay.
雷克斯 来 没事 没事的
Rex, come, it's okay, it's okay.
没事的
It's okay.
我会保证你的安全
I'm gonna keep you safe.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what we're gonna do,
但我们不会再回到那里了
but we're not going back there.
紫心勋章 美国士兵在执行军事任务期间受伤或阵亡得到的勋章
我一直在考虑
So, I've been thinking,
我不想再重新应征了
I don't think I'm gonna re-enlist.
你是怎么想的
How do you feel about that?
想不想跟我一起住
You wanna come live with me?
你刚刚放屁了吗
Did you just fart?
太恶心了
That's disgusting.
现在你又要在我讲话的时候睡觉
And now you're falling asleep while I talk to you?
你有什么计划吗
I mean, do you have any plans?
我的计划就是走一步看一步
My plan is just to figure it out as I go along.
过平民生活
The civilian life.
你想过那种通俗的生活
You wanna live that pop life?
那是什么
What is that?
你要成为天命真女组合的第四名成员吗
You're gonna be the fourth member of Destiny's Child?
不是的
Not exactly, no.
那不是我的计划
That wasn't my plan.
现在我给你两周的时间
Now, I'm gonna give you two weeks,
你会觉得无聊头顶
and you're gonna be bored out your mind.
我打赌 到时候你会回来 求我让你重返岗位
I bet you'll be back in my office begging for your job back.
但我被炸飞了 所以
Yeah, but I was blown up, so...
无聊的生活似乎更适合现在的我
Boring sounds really great right now.
我知道你最近过的不好
I know it's been some rough times recently,
但我希望你还没准备好时
but I just don't want you to rush into something
先不要急着放弃
that you're not ready to get into,
尤其是一份你热爱的工作
especially when this is something you love.
这确实是我所爱的 但是我...
It is what I love, but I...
我确定我找到了更爱的人 并且...
Pretty sure I found something, someone that I love even more, and, um...
其实 我一直在考虑
Well, actually, I was wondering,
我希望你能给我写封推荐信
I was hoping that you would write me a letter
支持我收养他
supporting me to adopt him.
当然可以 我会的 下士
Well, of course I will, Corporal.
你认为我疯了吗
You think I'm crazy?
这个问题有什么陷阱吗 就像...
Oh, is that a trick question? Like...
不 我是认真的
No, I'm being serious.
离开海军陆战队
What, for leaving the Marines?
是的
Yeah.
不 绝对不行
No, absolutely not.
你服完役了
You did your time.
你什么时候归队
Hey, when's your tour up?
我已经归队了
It was up...
一周以前
A week ago.
现在 我归另一个分队了
Now, I'm theirs for another 51.
好吧 所以...
Okay, so...
你又入伍了
You re-upped?
是的
Yeah, I mean,
怎么 有问题吗
what, is that a problem?
没错
Yeah.
有问题
That's a problem.
喔 喔 等一下 梅根
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on, Megan.
梅根 你要干什么
Megan, what are you doing?
听着 你决定离开海军陆战队的时候
Look, you didn't ask me when you decided
也没征求我的意见 我也不希望你这么做
to leave the Marines, and I wouldn't expect you to.
这是你的决定 我很高兴...
Look, it's your decision. I'm happy...
别假装你不知道这么做会惹我生气
Don't pretend like you didn't know this would piss me off.
你表现得好像我们之前谈过这个话题一样
You act like we talked about this.
我怎么会知道你会生气
I mean, how the hell could I know that?
我不知道 但你没问我我很不爽
I don't know, but it sucks that you didn't.
他很温和 他很温和
He's tender, he's tender.
没事的
It's okay.
你想收养这只动物
You want to adopt this animal?
你知道你在做什么吗
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
他只是受惊了 他很温和 我说过的
He's scared and he's tender, like I said.
无法被收养
请不要这样写
Please don't write that.
无法被收养
你有没有听我说
Are you listening to me?
他只是在害怕而已 他讨厌戴狗罩
He's just scared and he hates this muzzle that he's wearing,
无意冒犯 他也不喜欢兽医
and no offense, but he's not a massive fan of being at the vet's either.
我一周后再见他
I'll see him again in a week.
好吧 能不能不要在上面这样写
Okay, but please don't leave that on his chart,
这样他们是不会让我收养他的
'cause they'll never let me adopt him.
我就是这个意思
That's the point.
你是不是有很大的权力之类的
Are you having some sort of like a power trip or something?
你不是应该帮助这些动物吗
Are you not supposed to be helping these animals?
你戳到了他的伤口
You poked him where he's hurt.
所以他才有反应
He reacted.
如果你被脚下五英尺埋的四十磅炸药炸飞
Let's set off 40 pounds of explosives five feet under you
看看你会不会喜欢被戳
and see how you like being poked afterwards.
拜托 求你了 把那些话从他的档案里删掉
Please, I'm begging you. Please take it out of his file!
- 雷克斯在哪 - 不知道
- Where's Rex? - No idea.
- 嘿 福曼 - 过来
- Hey, Forman. - Come on.
这是在搞什么
What's the deal?
让他准备好
I'm getting him ready.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
阿富汗需要他
They want him in Afghanistan.
什么 你到底在说什么
What? What are you talking about?
上面对他进行了重新调遣
They're redeploying him.
不 不会的 他早就被免除现役了
No, no, they took him off active duty.
我想他们改变主意了
Well, I guess they changed their minds.
你是他的训犬员吗
Are you his handler?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
嘿 混蛋 我们走
Hey, jerks. Let's go.
军士长
Gunny.
天啊 利维 你在这做什么
Jesus, Leavey, what are you doing here?
军士长 我...
Gunny, I...
我来跟你道歉 对不起弄乱了你的办公室
I came to say that I am sorry for messing up your office.
这是我听过最不真诚的道歉
Now that's the weakest apology I ever heard.
雷克斯还没准备好重新调遣
Rex is not ready to be redeployed.
不是我的命令
It's not my call.
兽医不同意你收养他
The vet disagrees with you.
他完全是另一条狗了
He's a different dog.
他变了
He has changed.
我帮不了你
I can't help you.
拜托 求你改掉他的类别
Please, please just change his classification
这样等他回来之后 我可以收养他
so that I can adopt him when he gets back,
如果他能回来
if he gets back.
你对这只动物的关心让人敬佩
Your concern for the animal is honorable.
你很爱他 我理解
You're devoted to him, and I understand that,
也理解你为什么会生气
and I understand why you're angry.
我没有生气 我只是想
I'm not angry, I am trying
在这个战争英雄生命的最后几年里
to give a war hero a home
为他提供一个家
for the last few years of his life.
如果我们不得不处置雷克斯
How would you feel if we had to put Rex down
因为他看见一个过马路的四岁孩子
because he bit the hand
手里拿着一把玩具枪
of a four-year-old he passes on the street?
就去咬了他的手 你会有什么感想
Just because the boy was holding a toy gun?
什么都可能发生
It happens.
我
I've...
我看到过父母的那种目光
I've looked into the parents' eyes before.
我知道那是什么感觉
I know what that feels like.
他们不是宠物
They aren't pets.
他们甚至不再是狗
They aren't even dogs anymore.
他们是战士
They're warriors,
他们之后会面临和我们一样的问题
and they come back with all the same issues we do.
我们并不是残忍 我们只是理智并且负责
We're not being cruel, we're being intelligent and responsible.
- 不 不要这样对雷克斯 - 很抱歉
- No, no, not to Rex. - I'm sorry.
真的很抱歉
I really am.
拜托
Please.
利维 放他去吧
Leavey, just let this one go.
拜托了 军士长
Please. Gunny.
拜托
Please.
听我说 利维 我很抱歉
Look, Leavey, I'm sorry.
听着
Look,
过几天他就要被空运离开这里了
he's being flown out in a couple of days.
如果你想跟他告个别 我可以帮你安排
If you wanna say goodbye to him, I can arrange that.
嘿
Hey.
对不起
I'm sorry.
梅根
Megan.
梅根 亲爱的
Megan, honey.
梅根
Megan!
怎么了
What?
梅根 穿上点衣服
Megan, put some clothes on.
- 怎么回事 - 看看谁最爱你
- What? - Who loves you?
怎么回事
What's going on?
快过来见见她
Come over here and meet her.
我还没给她取名字 我想让你来取
I didn't name her because I wanted you to,
但如果你不给她起名小公主
but if you don't call her.
那你一定是疯了
Lover Girl, I think you're crazy.
你在逗我吧
You've gotta be kidding me.
不 我没有
No, I'm not kidding you.
你觉得这样就能替代他
You thought you could just replace him?
亲爱的 我没想替代他 我只是
Honey, I'm not trying to replace him, I just...
听着 我知道你爱他 但 天啊
Look, I know you love him, but... Jesus Christ,
梅根 你现在一团糟 你不能因为一条狗
Megan, you're a mess. You can't let your whole life
就毁掉了自己的人生
fall apart over some dog.
一条狗
Some dog?
那条狗救了我的命
That dog saved my life.
- 去死吧 - 梅根
- Go to hell. - Hey, now, Megan,
你不能这样跟你妈妈讲话
you can't talk to your mother like that.
她在想办法帮你
She is trying to help you.
别管闲事了 吉姆
Get a job, Jim.
我们还没说完
We are not finished here.
你不能像个大英雄一样回到我家
You cannot come back to my house like some big war hero
只因为你很受伤 就这样跟我讲话
and talk to me like that just because you got hurt.
离我远点 妈
Back off, Mom!
你可以随便挥霍你自己的人生
You can screw up your life as much as you want.
但你绝不能毁掉我的生活
You cannot take it out on me.
赶紧回去跟我丈夫道歉
Go in there right now and apologize to my husband!
- 道歉 - 没错
- Apologize? - Yes!
跟这个家伙道歉
Apologize to this guy?
没错
Yes.
我还是不相信你因为这个混蛋离开了爸爸
I can't believe you left Dad for this douchebag.
你没有任何权利...
You have no goddamn right to...
那这样吧 跟你爸过吧
You know what... Go be with your father.
- 我受够了 - 太棒了
- I am done! - Gladly!
宝贝
Baby.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
别打开
Don't open it!
天啊 亲爱的
Jesus, baby, baby.
没事 没事 只是车而已
It's okay, it's okay. It's just a car.
是车的警报 亲爱的 没事的
It's the alarm, sweetie, it's okay.
没事了
It's all right.
你要干什么
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
你不知道车里面有多热吗
You have any idea how hot it is in there?
能有多热
How hot it is?
照顾好自己的宠物 混蛋
Take care of your animal, asshole.
我的宠物好的很 你是谁啊 疯了吗
My animal is fine. What are you, crazy?
精神病
Lunatic.
喂 我能找一下福曼吗
Hi. Hi, yeah, can I talk to Forman?
是雷克斯的事
It's about Rex.
我知道我一直打过来
Yeah, I know I keep calling.
梅根 你还好吗
Megan, how are you doing?
一年后
好久没有你的消息了
We haven't heard much from you.
我还好 好多了
I'm okay, I'm better.
什么方面
In what ways?
呃 我...
Well, I...
我看到或听到某些事 也不会经常发疯了
I don't flip out as much when I see or hear certain things.
但我还是不能
I still can't quite...
忍受任何真实的人际交往
Tolerate any real, um, human interaction.
连跟你们说话都让我有点乏味
Even you guys are kind of a drag.
睡眠怎么样
How are you sleeping?
偶尔会做噩梦
Just a few bad dreams.
什么内容
About?
大部分都是想他在做什么
Mostly imagining what he's doing.
希望他没有承受痛苦
Just hoping he's not in pain.
他随时都有可能死掉
He could die any day.
他可能现在就会死掉
He could be dead right now, and...
如果雷克斯现在在这 你会对他说什么
What would you say to Rex if he were here right now?
你知道他其实是条狗 对吧
Well, you know he's a dog, right?
可能听起来很肉麻 但是
This is gonna sound so cheesy, but...
- 抱歉 - 没关系
- Sorry. - It's okay.
我可能
I'd probably, um...
我要感谢他
I'd thank him for...
努力教会我什么是爱
Trying to teach me what love is.
你说努力是什么意思
What do you mean, trying?
他好像教会了你很多
It sounds like he taught you a lot.
这是晚饭吗
Is that dinner?
据说早餐是一天最重要的一餐
Well, they always said breakfast is the most important meal.
你今天过的好吗
How was your day?
去了互助小组吗
You go to group?
怎么样
How was it?
这个是给你的
Uh, so, uh, this came for you.
莫拉莱斯是谁
Who is Morales?
为什么他要送你大都会队的垃圾
Why is he sending you Mets crap?
他是我之前认识的一个人
He's just some guy I used to know.
我是不是要拿着猎枪追杀他
Yeah, some guy I'm gonna have to be chasing off with a shotgun?
宝贝
Baby,
我知道你现在感觉失去了一切
I know that you feel like you lost everything.
我知道这种感觉
I know what that feels like.
但问题在于 你要继续生活
But the thing is, you gotta keep living.
- 我在生活 - 不 你没有
- I am living. - No, you're not.
这不叫生活
This isn't living.
你要自己想清楚
You gotta figure out what it would take
怎么让生活变得有意义
to make it worth it.
雷克斯也值得这样的生活
Rex would be worth it.
你知道你要怎么做吗
You know what you gotta do?
他们不跟我谈 我把他遗弃了 我走了
They won't talk to me. I have abandoned him, I left.
那你就要想办法
Then you gotta find a way.
人生中只有几个人 是你要想办法追寻的
There are a few people in life, not many,
这样的人并不多
that you gotta find a way for.
如果你需要什么
If you needed something,
我愿意倾尽所有去帮你
I would do whatever it took,
并不是因为我是什么好爸爸
not because I'm any kind of great dad,
而是因为我对你的爱让我愿意改变
but because how I love you is stronger than what I'm not.
我希望你愿意走出门
I want you to be a person who shows up
工作
for work,
出席朋友的葬礼
for your friends' funerals,
过自己的生活
for life.
我试过 但失败了
I've tried, I failed.
那就再失败一次
So fail again.
一直失败到入土那一天
And just keep failing until they're tossing dirt on your corpse.
宝贝 你要奋斗
Baby, all you gotta do is fight,
你知道该怎么奋斗
and you know how to fight.
你可是海军陆战队的
You're a frickin' Marine.
对吧
Right?
我爱你
I love you.
我能把这个扔了吗
Can I toss this, please?
或者烧了
Maybe burn it?
谢谢
Please.
太恶心了
It's disgusting.
或者只把卡片留着
Actually, maybe just keep the card.
你也用不上
You don't need it.
我没法再等三周 才会有人给我回电话
I can't wait another three weeks for someone to call me back.
我就不能跟他说五分钟吗
Can I just talk to him for five minutes?
其实不是 是空军部的决定
Well, it's actually not. It's an Air Force decision.
军犬计划是由空军监管的
The Air Force oversees the canine program.
那你能告诉我他现在在哪吗
Well, then, can you tell me exactly where he is?
好 我知道现在听起来像个跟踪狂
Okay, look, I know I sound like a stalker here,
但我打电话是要找一个战争英雄
but I'm calling for a war hero.
- 喂 - 利维下士
- Hello? - Corporal Leavey.
我是福曼中士
It's Sergeant Forman.
我这周一直收到你的留言
I've been getting your messages all week,
所以我想最好还是给你回个电话
figured I better call you back,
看来你是我还没被炸得
seeing as you're the only reason
屁股开花的唯一理由了
I still have a complete set of butt cheeks.
是啊 我这周一直在给你打电话
Hey, yeah, I have been calling all week.
我只是想知道 雷克斯怎么样了
I guess I just wanted to know, how's Rex?
他想见你
He'd love to see you.
- 等一下 你说什么 - 雷克斯
- Wait, what? - Rex.
- 你还在吗 - 还在
- You there? - Yeah, uh...
他们最终决定让他退役了
They finally decided to retire him.
我想你应该来参加退役典礼
I just thought you might want to come to the ceremony.
当然
Yes, I'm...
但这意思是说 我可以收养他了吗
Does this mean that I can adopt him now?
不是这样 我看他的档案
I don't think so. I'm looking
上面还是写着不可收养
at his file and it says he's unadoptable.
我知道上面怎么写的 但是
I know what it says, I know, but, uh...
我是说 他有没有被重新评估呢
I mean, hasn't he been reassessed?
我不知道
I have no idea,
但现在档案中写的还是不可收养
but it still says unadoptable on his paperwork,
而且
and, uh...
他现在病得很严重 梅根
He's pretty sick, Megan.
有多严重
How bad is it?
如果你有什么想法 就尽量快点
If you're gonna try and do something, I'd do it fast.
国家退役老兵援助基金
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
查尔斯
舒默
纽约州议员
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
联系方式
办公地址
行程安排
邮件投递
参议员
Senator?
舒默参议员
Senator Schumer?
不好意思 能打扰您几分钟吗
Excuse me, can I just have a moment of your time?
我现在有事要处理
I'm in the middle of something.
我打电话已经打了好几周了
I've been calling for weeks.
是我在阿富汗的一个朋友的事
It's about my partner in Afghanistan.
他现在状况很不好 需要你的帮助
He's not doing well. He needs your help.
好的 我稍后联系你
All right, I'll get back to you later.
他叫雷克斯 是炸弹探测犬
Uh, his name is Rex. He's a bomb sniffer.
他在伊拉克挽救了成千上万的生命
He saved thousands of lives in Iraq.
这是我们在费卢杰
Here we are in Fallujah.
他找到了所有AK47步枪
He found all those AK-47s.
这是我们在拉马迪
And here we are in Ramadi,
这是他现在的样子
and, uh, here he is today.
他今年十岁了 如果我不能收养他
He's 10 years old, and if I can't adopt him,
他们就要对他安乐死
then they're gonna put him to sleep.
你说你叫什么名字
What did you say your name was?
梅根 抱歉
Uh, Megan, sorry.
梅根 利维下士
Corporal Megan Leavey.
很高兴见到你 下士
Oh, Very nice to meet you, Corporal.
我很荣幸
My pleasure.
先生 打扰 打扰一下
Um, sir, sir, excuse... Excuse me!
先生
Sir!
费恩 不要对别人大喊大叫
Finn, don't yell at people.
不然我怎么才能吸引他们的注意
How else am I supposed to get his attention?
你这样就把他吓跑了
You're literally scaring him away.
安静一点
Just be quiet.
和他们对话就好
Have a conversation with someone.
您好 在我领养陆战军犬的请愿书上签个字如何
Hi, sign my petition to adopt a veteran war dog?
什么意思
So, what is this for?
我想领养陆战军犬 这是请愿书
This is a petition for me to adopt my Marine war dog.
他现在病得很厉害 也很快就要退役了
He's very sick and his retirement ceremony's coming up,
所以我真心希望可以把他带回家领养
so I'm really hoping I get to bring him home.
你是海军陆战队员
You're the Marine?
谢谢
Thank you.
感谢你对他的帮助
Thank you for your service.
还不赖嘛
It's not that hard.
直播倒计时 五 四 三
We're live in five, four, three...
各位好 我是克里斯汀 约翰逊
Hi, I'm Kristine Johnson.
今天我们邀请了一位特别来宾
Today, we're joined by a very special guest.
感谢梅根来到我们节目 讲述你的故事
Thank you, Megan, for being here, and tell us your story.
为什么雷克斯对你来说这么重要
Why is Rex so important to you?
他真的是只特别棒的动物
Well, he's just an amazing animal,
我希望他的余生可以和他熟悉的喜欢的人
and I want him to be able to live the rest of his life
舒默参议员支持战争英雄 战争老兵领养成功
住在一个温暖的家里
in a happy home with someone that he knows and loves.
舒默参议员支持战争英雄 战争老兵领养成功
为什么他这个都做不到
And why can't he?
因为前不久他们觉得他会造成威胁
Um, because a while ago, they thought he was unsafe,
但其实他只是害怕了
but really, he was just scared,
可能还有点迷惑
and probably confused,
领养的好方法 做出改变 开始你的免费领养
可能和我当时的状态是一样的
probably just as confused and scared as I was at the time.
领养的好方法 做出改变 开始你的免费领养
你们一起在被炸飞过
And you were hit by an explosion together,
是一个爆破装置 是吗
an IED, isn't that right?
没错 二零零六年 我们在伊拉克受伤了
Yeah, in 2006, we were injured in Iraq.
但你们俩受伤之后
But despite your injuries,
还是继续执行了任务是吗
the two of you continued the mission.
- 没错 - 太棒了
- That's right. - That's amazing.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
我看到有两万...
Now, I read that you have 22...
两万两千人
Twenty-two thousand.
两万两千人在你的请愿书上签字了
Twenty-two thousand names on your petition.
没错
Yes!
这样的支持对你有帮助吗
That kind of support, is it helping?
希望有所帮助 但现在还不好说
Well, we hope it is, but it's too early to tell.
祝你好运 梅根 我们在这为你加油
Good luck, Megan, we're really pulling for you here.
非常感谢
I appreciate it.
走吧
Go ahead.
稍等
Hold there.
我是来参加退役典礼的
I'm here for the retirement ceremony.
去操场吧 下士
Head to the fields, Corporal.
走吧
There you go.
嘿 我认识你
Hey, I know you.
你是电视上那个有名的战地英雄对吧
Yeah, you're, uh, that famous war hero, right, that's on TV?
大都会球迷
Big-time Mets fan.
你怎么在这
What are you doing?
你回来了
You're back.
是啊
Yeah, yeah.
我来参加 奇科的退役典礼
I'm, uh, here for Chico's retirement,
两天后就归队了 去海军陆战队营地
then I ship back out in two days, Camp Leatherneck.
对那里永远都厌倦不了
Can't get enough of that place.
之后就结束了
After that, that's it.
该回家了
Time to come home.
我听说今天雷克斯今天也要退役
So, I hear Rex is retiring today, too.
没错
Yeah, I...
我在收集签名 还是想把他带回家
Trying to get signatures, still trying to bring him home.
你还要给自己惹上麻烦吗
Are you gonna get in some faces again?
可能还要打几架
Start a couple brawls, maybe?
给对方一个锁喉 再把他击倒
Put someone in a choke hold, knock someone out?
如果走投无路的话我会的
Yeah, yeah, if I have to, yeah.
抱歉 我没给你回电话
Sorry, I haven't called you back. I...
没事的
It's all good.
听我说
Look,
是时机不对
it wasn't our time.
起码最后有个家伙得到了这个姑娘
At least one Marine gets the girl in the end.
你要知道 你惊动了指挥部每一层
You know, you rattled every chain in the command, right?
我可能要成为透露这个大新闻的人了
I get to be the one to break the big news.
最好趁他们没改变心意赶紧把他带走
Better take him home before they change their minds.
雷克斯
Rex!
欢迎回家
Welcome home!
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
喜欢吗
You like it?
坐下 真乖 那是什么
Sit, good boy, what's that?
是什么啊
What is that? What's that?
这个呢 你喜欢足球吗
What about this? You like a football?
你喜欢这个吧
You like that, you like that?
这是你最爱的
Oh, this is your favorite one.
这是你的女朋友
Here's your girlfriend. Here's your girlfriend.
没错
Yeah, yeah.
咬到我的手了
You've got my hand, you've got my hand.
你现在看起来不那么凶悍了 我的军犬
You don't look so tough right now, war dog.
天啊 你被宠坏了
God, you're spoiled.
就这样吧
There you go.
没事的
It's okay.
不要怕
Don't be scared.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
今天是退伍军人感恩日
today is Veterans Appreciation Day,
请欢迎两位特殊的洋基球迷
so please join us in welcoming two very special Yankees fans.
紫心勋章获得者 梅根 利维下士
Purple Heart recipient Corporal Megan Leavey,
以及雷克斯中士
and Sergeant Rex.
雷克斯中士 编号一六八
Sergeant Rex, Echo 168,
因执行炸弹巡逻任务时表现优异
was recognized for his superior performance of duty
而被公认为是一条出色的军犬
while serving as a patrol explosive military working dog.
去吧 海军陆战队
Go Marines! Yeah! Whoo!
不是吧
No!
海军陆战队营地 阿富汗
快拿下去
Get this off me!
雷克斯中士和利维下士
Sergeant Rex and Corporal Leavey,
无私的奉献
through their sacrifice together,
挽救了无数人的生命 所以今天
saved countless human lives, and so today,
我们要感激他们
we thank them.
亲爱的 你出名了
Famous, baby, you're famous.
雷克斯直至2012年12月去世都与梅根生活在一起
雷克斯
Hey, Rex.
去拿那个玩具
Get that toy.
我去帮你拿吧
I'll get it for you.
从海军陆战队退役后 梅根继续担任炸弹探测犬"爱国者"的训犬师
服务的客户包括联合国和洋基体育场
如今 梅根在新泽西州担任兽医技术员
纪念爱犬雷克斯
一九九九年四月至二零一二年十二月
你在叫什么
What you barking at?
伙计
Hi, buddy.
真乖
Good boy.